Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administration files [2016 processing project], Circa 1963 - Circa 2012; Series 14
  - Private & Parochial, 1968-1971; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Elementary Tours, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - College & Adult Tours, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Weekend Docentry, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Docent Schedule, Correspondence, 1971; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Worksheets, 1968-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - S.O.P. ( Standard Operating Procedure), 1961-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Manual for Photo-Project Leaders (T-69), 1969; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Quarterly Report, 1969 April 1 - May 31; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - S.G., Undated; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Press Release - S.G. / L.A., Undated; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Special Projects loose info., 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - Puppet Show, 1969 February; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - African Show - April 4-26 1969, 1969 April 4-26; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Education Dept. Memos/Corresp./Planning, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - CGA/CSA Summer '69 Projects & Programs, 1969; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Pre-School Workshop, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Tower Office Correspondence 1969, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Memo 1969, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Memo 1970, Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - D.C. School System 1968-69, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Corresp. 1968-70, 1968-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Sunday Membership Workshop A69-70, 1969-70; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Press Releases / Area Exhibitions 69/70, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Education Department Projects & Exhibitions, 1972-1976; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Reimbersement Requests to Dept. of Corrections, Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hattie M. Strong Foundation, 1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Education Dept. American Collection, 1973-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Community Arts Programs / Organizations, 1974-1977; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Columbian October 1975, 1975 October; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Public Schools - Art, 1975-1976; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Resumes 1972-1974, Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Workshop thoughts, proposals, etc. 1974, Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - American Drug Abuse Ed - Reaction Project A.D.A.E.P, 1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Art / Education Proposals, 1968-1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lorton Programs 1972-1973, Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Day Care (Institute), 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Advisory News Letter, 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Bill Snyder Association (Maryland Institute for the Blind), 1973 March 7; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Supply + Equipment Request Receipts, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - CGA Staff Development Special Education Projects Department, 1971 October 1; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Reimbursement Checks from N.C.A. C.D.C.A., 1972-1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bi-Monthly Bi-Annual Annual Reports - C.G. of A., Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lorton: In-House / Correspondence 74-75, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Receipts, 1972-1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Budgets & Reports, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Receipts, 1971-1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Fine Arts 1974 Commission Incoming Correspondence, 1973-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence (Outgoing), 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Veterans Administration, 1973-1974; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Fine Arts Commission Reimbursement Request & Corresponding Data / Budget, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - D.C. Fine Arts Commission Reimbursement + Requests / Forms 1974, Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Manuel Copy Lesson Plan info., 1973; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Loose Documents and Correspondence (1), 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Loose Documents and Correspondence (2), 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Press Coverage 1971-72, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Loose Documents, 1971-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Lorton - Youth Center, 1972-1975; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Dupont Center, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Cga Spec. Education Projects Dept.: Comprehensive Sched. for Art Activities - DACAS, 1972 January 5; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Project 370 - Scope, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Children's Gallery 1967-1968, Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - "Light and Art", 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Graduate School USDA (1), 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School USDA (2), 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Art Auction Brandeis-Unesco, 1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - WETA 1967-68, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Ft. Mayers Art Club May 2nd, 1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Dept. of Education 1963-66, 1963-1966; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Education -- Selby, 1965-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CGA Evaluation Sheets 1968-69, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Children's Gallery 1968-69, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1968 Docent SOP, Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - to be answered, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Tour Requests 1968-69, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Inner Office Correspondence 1968, Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - S.O.P. Tour Schedule 1968-70, 1968-1970; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Teacher's Notes & Repros. 68-69, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - School Blurbs 1967-68, Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Letters-1967-68, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence CG & Tours 67-68, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Children's Gallery Printed Information, Circa 1962-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Gallery Memo_1967-68, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Quarterly Reports 1965-67, 1965-1967; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Budget - Education Department 1967-68, 1967-1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Plans - Children's Museum, 1966-1967; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - CG Summer Program Statistics, 1967; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Volunteers, 1968; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sources, 1967; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - News Clippings: Docents, The Corcoran, Children's Gallery, 1961-1966; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Education Photographs, Circa 1962-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Old Schedule Forms Summer Children's Gallery, Circa 1962-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Prints 1966, Circa 1962-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Architecture Show Children's Gallery 1970, Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Junior Museum 1950-59, 1950-1959; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - George Vantongerloo, 1980 April 22 - 1980 June 17; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vantongerloo Grant Proposal, 1980 April - 1980 May; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vantongerloo Lecture, Undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vantongerloo, Undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vantongerloo, Undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Statistics-Nigeria, Undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Resource Materials "Treasures of Ancient Nigeria", 1980 Decmber - 1981 January; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - P.H. Polk Photography, 1981 March 21 - 1981 May 17; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Charles Peale Polk Painting Summer '81, 1905 June 3; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Recollections: 10 Women Photographers, 1905 June 3; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Neil Jenney Paintings, 1981 September 11 - 1981 November 1; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Art Tomorrow, 1981 October 14; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Of Time and Place Mixed Media Genre, 1981 September 22 - 1981 November 15; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - On Going Dialogue Blaine Larson/Andrew Hudson, 1981 December 15 - 1982 February 7; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Black Folk Art Reference & Information, 1981 Novmber - 1982 March; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Black Folk Art Mixed Media, 1982 January 15 - 1982 March 28; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Atget: Old France, 1982 January 9 - 1982 February 21; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Circus Art: Center Ring Mixed Media, 1982 April 24 - 1982 June 6; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - [Grants & MFA Houston], Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - AAM/Accreditation, 1994; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - AAM Conference/April, 1994; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - [Museum Leadership Proposal, Rhode Island School of Design, Utah Musum of Art], 1994; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - [Hudson Museum, Institute of Museum Services, Milton Museum], 1994; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - [Proposals], Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Harvard's IMS Proposal, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - IMS, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - IMS Proposal: 1989, Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - IMS, 1993; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - IMS, 1994; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - IMS, 1995; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - IMS 1995-1996, Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - IMS, 1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - IMS, 1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - IMS Award for Museum Service, 1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Museum Education: Handicapped, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Job Descriptions, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Ed. Department: Staff/Response Profile, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - IMS Award, Circa 1988-1996; Series 14 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Technology & CGA, 1998; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Art Museums & Technology, 1993-1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Susan Badder Correspondence, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Environmental Film Festival, 1995; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Sweet Briar College Arts Mgt. Class, 1998 January; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Loose Documents, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Maida Withers / Improv Performance, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Storytellinggs Collabboration w/ MLK Library, 1997; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - DCPS Arts & Humanities Initiative, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Senior Outreach Program, 1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Outreach/Seniors/FHSO fy99, 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Education Dept. Program FY96, 1996-1997; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Exhibition Statistics 1995-96, 1995-1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Camera Receipts, 1996-1997; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - VACOP/CAVA, 1997; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Account Memos fy97, 1997-1998; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - NEA Grants 1998-99, 1998-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Dept. Finance Report Education, 1994 July 1 - December 31; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Unscheduled Tour Forms, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Teacher Resource 1998, 1998 March - December; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Weekday/Weekend Docents fy99, 1999-2000; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Langley HS Partnership, 1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - School Transportation 1997-2000, Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Work Study Students 1995-96, 1995-1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Exhibition Stats, 1994-1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Schoo Transportation Information FY97, 1997-2000; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Museum Mission Statement, Circa 1995-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Summer Institute for Educator, 1998; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - CGA Rockwell Art Exhibit Clipping, 2000; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Special Tour Request fy98, 1996-1998; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Account Memos fy99, 1998-1999; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Headstart, 1995; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Museum Education Department fy00, 2000; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Youthlink Meeting, 1995; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Office Memos / Request, 1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - MER Museum Education Roundtable, 1995-1996; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Project Accord / Metro Mania, 1996 May 23; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - DC Family Policy Seminar 1995, Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Unlock Door The Play, 1997; Series 14 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - [Stanford, Denver, Indiana], Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 1989-90 Goals & Budget Development, 1989-1990; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - [Advance Exhibition Schedule], Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Budget-Financial Year, 1992-1993; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - FY90-91 Budget & Plans, 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Departmental Budget, 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Proposal Departmental Budget, 1990; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - [Loose Project Documents], Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - High School Academy & Professional Training, 1989; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Education Outreach Propsals NEA, 1989 June 1; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Museum School Initiatives, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Bea Taylor's Audience Survey, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Lecture Stats, 1985-1986; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Intro Tour Forms, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Into. Talk Stats, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Thursday Evening Lectures Attendance Stats, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Education Department Statistics, 1980-1985; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Satistics 1992, 1991-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 1989-1990 Statistics, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 1995 Statistics, Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - American Decorative Arts, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Citicism + Abstract Expressionism, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Potential Speakers, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - [Loose French Documents], Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Megatrends 2000 Directors for the 1990, Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - DC Area Institutions, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Arts, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Europa, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Baltimore Musuem of Art, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Maryland Maryland Arts, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - NY, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Out of State Art Institutions, Circa 1980-1992; Series 14 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Atrium Floor Costs, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Workshop Space, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Space Planning, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Employee Benefits, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Column Cleaning, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Roof Study (St. Louis) 10/89, 1989 October 1; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Facilities Use, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Museum Committee Meetings, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Tom Thompson, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Roy Dommor, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - David Levy's Memos, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Marketing Plan FY91, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Long Range Planning - Bbruckman Rep. 1989, Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Gallery Cartoons, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - US - Japan Cultural Exchange, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Senior Staff Meet. Notes, 1988; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - 1990-91 Trustee Committee Assign., 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Museum Committee Meetings, 1991; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - All-Staff Orientation, 1989; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Staff Development Meetings, 1988-1989; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Committe on Works of Art, 1988; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Comm. Voluntarism '88 - '89, 1988-1989; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Smithsonian Institution Volunteers packet, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Board of TES - 1990, Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Salary Study - AAM, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Christmas Trees, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Trustees & Senior Staff Addresses, 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Women's Committee, 1990; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee - 90', 1990; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Voluntarism - Info. 1988-90, 1988-1990; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - CGA Volunteer/Docent Information, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Meeting of the Museum Board of Overseers Wednesday, 3-5pm, 1992 May 27; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Barbara Moore Ed TES Meeting, 1990 June 19; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Trustee Ed. Committee Meetings 1980-89, 1980-1989; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Tour Statistics 1980-81, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - "Best Building in Wash" Wash Post Article by Ben Forgey, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Beaux Arts/CGA Article 1976, Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - News Article on Workshop Progs, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Reviews & News Hems-Corcoran Magazine Articles, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Magazine Review of: Of Time + Place Lectures Packet, 1982; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Architecture - Washington - Articles, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - News Clips - CGA & Other Museums, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Thursday Evening Tours, 1980 July-August; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Mobil Open Night Tours 80-81, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Tour Statistics 1981-82, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Information Desk, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - CGA Museum ed 1991,2,3, 1991-1993; Series 14 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - TRS Ideas, Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Langley HS (Fairfax), Circa 1989-1992; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Educator Workshop, 2001 May 12; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - School Lists, 1999-2002; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - TRS 2001-2002, Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - DCPS Grant Proposal, 2002; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Treasures of the Soul, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - TRS- Teacher Resource Service - FY2002, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - TRS - Plan, Partnerships, Educ. Memberships, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - TRS - Clark Winchole, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - TRS 2002-2003, Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Turning The Page, 2002; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Loose Papers, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Brazil: Body & Soul Curriculum Guide for Educators, 2001; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Loudon County Art Teachers: CGA Staff Development Day, 2002 May 11; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - CGA School Reference Guide, 1998 March; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - TRS (#3) 2000-2001, Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Susan Badder Notes, Correspondence, and Other, Circa 1993-2006; Series 14 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - [Loose Photos], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - FY95 Education Department, 1995; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - FY97 Education Department, 1997; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - FY98 Education Department, 1998; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - MBOO/Education & Audience, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - MBOO/Edcuation Committees, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - MBOO Education, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - [Handwritten Exhibition Notes], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - DC Art Education Association, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Maryland Art Education Association, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - EdComm, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Museum Education Roundtable, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - MBOO Education Committee, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - MBOO, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - MBOO, 1999-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Community Advisory Board, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - CAB: Educational Programs, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - [Loose Disabilities Documents], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - [Loose Disabilities Documents], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - List ASAFO, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - List Churches, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - List General, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  - [Contacts], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  - Lila Wallace Community Office, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  - Summer Youth Partnership, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  - Community Advisory Board, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - [Loose Community Advisory Board Communications], Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Community Advisory Board Meeting Agendas/Minutes, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Community, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Community Advisory Board Communications, Circa 1995-2000; Series 14 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - [Andrew Stevovich], Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Dudley, Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Dudley Lecture 2002, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Dudley 2001, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Dudley Lecture 2001, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - The Dudley Lecture 2000, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Catlett (Dudley 2000), Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - The Dudley Lecture 1999, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Dudley Lecture 1994, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Dudley Lecture 1993, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Dudley Lecture 1991, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Dudley Lecture 1989, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Dudley Lecture 1990, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Dudley Lecture 1988, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Dudley Lecture 1987, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Dudley Lecture Finances 1986, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Dudley Lecture Final Report 1986, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Dudley Lecture Suggestions for Future Lectures, Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Dudley Lecture 1986, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Dudley Lecture Finances 1985, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Dudley Lecture 1984, Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Dudley Lecture Original Agreement, Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - [Unlabeled Cassette Tape], Circa 1984-2002; Series 14 (Box 51, Folder 23)